<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Lists on blank </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://blank.mdhender.com/tags/lists/index.xml/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <author>Michael D Henderson</author>
    
    <updated>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 13:57:47 CST</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Taxonomies</title>
      <link>http://blank.mdhender.com/post/overview-of-taxonomies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 13:57:47 CST</pubDate>
      <author>Michael D Henderson</author>
      <guid>http://blank.mdhender.com/post/overview-of-taxonomies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; has an exceptionally flexible system for organizing and indexing your content: taxonomies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I visualize taxonomies as a sort of encyclopedia. It&amp;rsquo;s a really odd encyclopedia because every volume of
my metaphorical set is about a different topic. There&amp;rsquo;s a volume on chimpanzees and a volume on baseball
players and one on Shakespeare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another odd thing about this set is that none of the volumes contain any articles. Open one to any
page and all you&amp;rsquo;ll find is a link to the article. The articles are stored in a separate file cabinet.
That allows articles to be referenced in multiple volumes. For example, my post on a tribe of baseball
playing chimpanzees named The Shakespeares could be included in three separate volumes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can accept the metaphor, then it&amp;rsquo;s not much of a leap to say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taxonomy - a volume of the encyclopedia. It can contain any number of articles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Term - the name of an article. It&amp;rsquo;s the key used to find the actual article. Terms are unique within a taxonomy. The same term can appear in multiple taxonomies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Content - the article. The content of the article can be referenced from any number of taxonomies but can only be referenced by one term.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>